[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Shadow Punisher]
[Divine Constable Tally]
[Episode 13]
Don't run! Stop!
Got you now!
Get her!
Stop!
My Lords.
This girl ran away from the mansion.
We are teaching her a lesson
on behalf of our Master.
We won't bother...
So many of you
beating a child.
Have you no shame?
Jiuying.
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
If you want,
come back with us.
Watch out.
There it is!
Run!
Oh my goodness.
This must be the real green-haired demon.
There really is a demon in Mingling County.
After them!
If what the note says is true
and Gong Sihai is selling government salt,
I'm afraid the waters in Mingling County
are much deeper than we thought.
This is...
A Chiying bug.
I've searched high and low for this.
I didn't expect
to find it here.
No wonder it's called Chiying.
It must be
named after
its glowing wings.
This tiny bug
can actually mutate people into demons.
Could the Gong family
also be related to the Liluo Dark Night?
Old Geezer said that
these Chiying bugs
love to gather around graves.
Could it be that in this lake...
Let's go down and find out.
It's Zhenzhu, Yan, and the others.
Let's go help them first.
Anyway, a lake this big
won't run away on its own.
Yan.
What happened?
Let me tell you.
My eyes were really opened today.
There really is a green-haired demon.
It was covered in green hair.
It looked like a wolf,
but for some reason,
it became demonic.
What?
Yan isn't exaggerating.
We originally wanted
to save Xia Jiuying,
but a wolf appeared all of a sudden
and carried her away.
Although it's a wolf,
its body has completely mutated.
It doesn't look like a normal animal at all.
Where is the mutated wolf
now?
How can two legs
outrun four paws?
We couldn't catch up.
It also snatched
Huang Bingshui away.
Speak.
I'll speak!
We were
running ahead.
Then we heard a scream
and saw Huang Bingshui
being carried away by that demon wolf.
Was he eaten?
We didn't dare to look.
Only drip-shaped bloodstains
were found at the scene.
Judging from this,
he must have been bitten
and taken away.
Strange.
Why did it take Huang Bingshui away?
It must be...
It must be Xia Jiuying
who made that monster do it.
Huang Bingshui
often beat that girl.
Tell me,
how did Zhe Shan
treat Xia Jiuying?
He always beat and scolded her.
Zhenzhu,
do you suspect that
Xia Jiuying ordered the demon wolf
to maul Zhe Shan to death?
I think
it's really possible.
A green-haired demon appeared in Mingling County.
Under Xia Jiuying's orders,
it mauled the boxer Zhe Shan to death,
carried the body
into Mount Fuyao,
and dumped it in the Yan River.
It all adds up.
Anyway,
let's find him first.
Are they leaving us here?
Mount Fuyao is this way.
My Lords!
-My Lords, please let us go. -My Lord, please let me down!
-My Lords! -My Lords!
My Lord,
we found nothing.
My Lords,
Mount Fuyao is huge.
We've been searching all night.
Are you sure it's in this direction?
Huang Bingshui was injured last night.
The wound should have clotted by now.
Would there still be bloodstains on the ground?
Blood can clot,
but the smell won't.
Found him! Found him!
Found him! He's here!
Help!
Here!
My Lord! My Lord!
Save me...
Save me!
This bite mark
matches the one on Zhe Shan's throat
perfectly.
What did I tell you?
It must be that girl seeking revenge
by setting the wolf on him.
No.
If it was for revenge,
why didn't he die instantly
with a crushed throat like Zhe Shan?
My Lord, save me.
Just save me,
and I'll tell you everything.
Ji Ada did it all.
Ji Ada did it all!
I was forced into it!
Stop dawdling.
Spit it out.
I'll tell you everything.
Twelve years ago,
Ji Ada took a few of us
up the mountains to hunt wolves.
We ran into Xia Jiuying's mother.
Seeing that she was somewhat pretty,
he harbored lecherous thoughts.
But she resisted aggressively
and even bit Ji Ada.
In a fit of anger,
he ordered me to release the dogs.
Those were hunting dogs.
They were very fierce.
About 4 or 5 of them surrounded the woman
and bit her to death.
What?
So Xia Jiuying's mother
wasn't killed by wolves.
She was killed by you
animals!
No, it wasn't me!
Divine Constable,
Ji Ada made me do it.
I had no choice.
Does Xia Jiuying
know about this?
No.
Once out of the woods,
no one ever mentioned it again.
Ji Ada put out the word
that the woman
was mauled by wolves.
If anyone let it slip,
he'd cut their tongue out.
But Ji Ada said
he was the one who collected
her mother's body.
Bah!
Killing someone
and burying them on the spot
is hardly considered collecting a body.
I still remember
where she was buried.
It's just a little further ahead.
I can take you there.
But now,
there's nothing left there.
I've already given
the last skull
to Xia Jiuying.
She kept you alive
just so you could point out
the burial spot?
Yes.
Xia Jiuying has been looking for her mother
for so many years.
Didn't she
ask you before?
Of course she did.
But who would
dare to tell her?
Later, Xia Jiuying grew up
to be foolish
but skilled at hunting.
So Ji Ada took an interest in her.
Ji Ada
came up with a
wicked idea to use the dead
to control the living.
Every once in a while,
he would dig up a bone and toss it to her.
To get
her mother's bones,
Xia Jiuying had to work for him.
After 5 years,
the whole skeleton
is now only missing a skull.
A bunch of animals!
Now tell me.
When the dogs were released
to maul Xia Jiuying's mother to death,
was Zhe Shan there?
Yes.
Yes, he was there too!
He was leading one of the dogs.
You used the bones of a loved one
to threaten a child!
You're all worse than animals!
My Lords,
please have mercy!
Please have mercy.
For the sake of me helping Xia Jiuying
find her mother,
please spare me.
Just now,
I dug up that skull
and gave it to her.
Please spare me.
Let me go, My Lord.
My Lord, My Lord.
Please spare me.
My Lords, you don't know this,
but that Hound Pit
hides other secrets.
If you spare me,
I will confess everything.
I will confess everything!
My Lord, please spare me.
Please spare me!
Lord Situ.
Please
escort this man back to the county office
for overnight interrogation.
Leave the rest
to us.
Yes.
Take him away.
Please spare me...
My Lord!
Move!
I didn't expect
this child to have such a hard life.
If Xia Jiuying
really ordered the wolves to kill,
even if she is pitiful,
the law will not tolerate it.
Xia Jiuying.
Go away!
I want to be with my mother.
Mother, I will protect you.
That should be her mother.
Xia Jiuying,
listen to me.
We won't hurt you,
nor will we hurt your mother.
We are here to help you.
Liars!
Liars...
You are all liars!
Lying to me,
you are all lying to me!
We are not lying to you.
Trust me.
As long as you tell us the truth,
we will definitely find a way to help you.
Tell me.
Was it you
who controlled your demon wolf friend
to maul Zhe Shan to death?
They all deserve to die!
They
killed my mother...
This was stuck in my mother's bones.
I recognize it.
It's a dog fang.
It's a dog fang!
It wasn't a wolf that bit my mother to death.
It was a dog,
and the person holding the leash!
It was Ji Ada,
Huang Mazi,
and Zhe Shan!
They all deserve to die!
They deserve it!
They all deserve to die.
They deserve it...
They all deserve to die!
They deserve it.
They all deserve to die.
They deserve it! They deserve it!
They all deserve to die!
I'm begging you!
Don't take me away.
I'm begging you...
I want to stay with her a little longer.
I want revenge.
I also want
to live.
It is indeed a dog's fang.
So,
she knew everything.
She has been away
♪ A solitary boat dividing left and right ♪
from home for too long.
♪ Amidst the vast, misty waters, they sail toward the surging tide ♪
I'm begging you...
Please...
♪ The rust of old memories feels like a waking dream ♪
Mother.
♪It hurts to let go, but I'm holding tightly to emptiness♪
I will protect you.
I won't let anyone
♪ Should we meet across mountains and seas ♪
separate us.
♪ If the long road leads to no return ♪
♪ If I can't travel with you in this life ♪
The stars in the sky
♪ If the lights in my heart ♪
are blinking.
♪ Become old marks with the falling snow ♪
Where will mother stop on her journey?
♪ I'll reminisce with you in the next life ♪
Every star
♪ Your hesitant steps back then ♪
is a light,
♪ If the years flow by like river waters, how can they be held back? ♪
guiding mother safely through the night.
♪ Should we meet across mountains and seas ♪
♪ If the long road leads to no return ♪
♪ If I can't travel with you in this life ♪
What a sin.
Arrest her if you want.
♪ If the lights in my heart ♪
I can't bring myself to do it.
♪ Become old marks with the falling snow ♪
Xia Jiuying.
I understand your difficulties.
♪ I'll reminisce with you in the next life ♪
But the state has its laws, and the family has its rules.
You let the wolf kill Zhe Shan.
You must return to the county office with us.
My colleagues,
I hope you've been well.
Lou Tianming?
They are here.
They are here!
Everyone,
we're taking Xia Jiuying
and breaking out of here.
It really is you,
Lou Tianming!
Yan Zige?
You're alive?
[Demonic Overlord, Yan Zisheng]
My brother died at the hands of the Divine Constable Bureau.
Today, I
will avenge him!
Don't kill Big Wolf.
Don't kill Big Wolf!
-During my absence, -Don’t kill Big Wolf!
has the Bureau been well?
How dare you ask?
I used to treat you as a brother.
I, Yan Sanhuo, was blind
not to see your cruel nature!
Lou.
It's been over a month since we parted.
I've missed you very much.
Since you went to work elsewhere,
why didn't you say goodbye
to everyone first?
Lord Li,
you've been promoted to Divine Constable.
I must
congratulate you.
The Divine Constable Bureau
only has four Divine Constables.
Four spots for 4 people.
If you didn't leave, Lou,
how would there be a place for me?
Qingyang,
your sharp tongue
is wasted at the Divine Constable Bureau.
Why don't you come with me?
Lou,
you're on a bad luck streak lately.
If I follow you,
I'd surely lose.
Your brother's revenge
can be taken today!
Zhenzhu, you protect her.
I haven't had a good fight
in a long time.
Kill!
Yan!
How did you become such a freak?
Watch out!
Big Wolf!
-Jiuying. -Big Wolf!
What a splendid demonized creature!
Such a pity.
Anyone who opposes Liluo
is asking for death.
No, Big Wolf!
No!
Big Wolf!
-Big Wolf! -Jiuying!
Big Wolf...
Big Wolf!
No...
No, don't die, Big Wolf!
Don't die, Big Wolf!
No!
No...
Don't die, Big Wolf!
Big Wolf! Big Wolf!
Big Wolf!
No!
Don't die, Big Wolf!
No! No!
Lou Tianming escaped,
but he's badly injured.
Knowing his temperament,
he likely won't make any rash moves
in the near future.
Xia Jiuying.
You knew all along
they would come after us,
didn't you?
Tell me,
why did those demon-men
want to kill you?
Because...
T-They caught Big Wolf
and took it
to a glowing cave.
There were bugs.
A glowing cave?
Bugs?
Where is the cave?
Do you remember?
Xia Jiuying.
-Go away! Go away! -Tell me!
-Go away! -Meng Rui.
-She's in shock now. -Big Wolf.
-I’m afraid she won't be -Big Wolf.
speaking up for a while.
-But... -Big Wolf...
I believe
she must know the location of the cave.
Otherwise,
Lou Tianming wouldn't have chased her all the way here
to silence her.
Give her some time.
Big Wolf...
For now,
we should first
close the case in Mingling County.
Isn't the case solved?
The green-haired demon is dead.
The real culprit of the floating corpse case is here.
Isn't it all solved?
Brother Sanhuo.
A so-called shocking case
is not that easy to solve.
[Mingling County Government]
Officers.
No need to trouble yourselves.
I'll confess.
I'll confess everything!
Move.
Hurry up.
Lord Situ.
Move.
Lord Li.
Wait a minute.
[Breezes of Grace and Harmony]
Alright, Jiuying.
I know
you still have concerns in your heart.
But don't worry.
We will give a proper burial
to your mother.
We will bury her
in the place you carefully chose for her.
Mother.
Mother...
Mother. Mother.
Mother.
Mother...
Silly child.
It's okay.
Get up.
It's okay. It's okay.
Jiuying,
listen to me.
[Breezes of Grace and Harmony]
This
is the prison of the county government.
You will temporarily
stay here for now.
Lord Situ.
[Breezes of Grace and Harmony]
Deep down, Jiu Ying
is not a bad child.
Please
don't treat her harshly.
[Integrity, Impartiality, Prudence, and Diligence]
Lord Li.
Please rest assured.
I will have someone take good care of her.
Go.
[Integrity, Impartiality, Prudence, and Diligence]
Lord Situ,
there are 2 more things
I need your help with.
First,
please send someone to keep an eye on the Gong Mansion.
During this time,
if anyone tries to flee,
arrest them immediately.
Second,
go to the county
and find some good swimmers,
the kind who are good at diving, holding their breath,
and salvaging underwater.
I will do as you say.
My Lords,
I will take my leave now.
An invitation?
[Respectfully from the Ji Family]
An invitation from the Ji family.
This Ji Ada is quite bold.
We haven't even settled the score with him
for letting his dogs maul someone to death,
yet he comes to us himself.
Interesting.
The person who delivered the invitation said
it's to thank the Divine Constable Bureau
for solving the case brilliantly
and successfully catching
Zhe Shan's murderer.
He's holding some kind of appreciation banquet.
[Invitation]
He's certainly well-informed.
The suspect was just locked up in prison,
and he's already hosting a banquet.
He doesn't even consider
the blood on his hands.
Then what are we waiting for?
Every wrong has its cause, every debt has its debtor.
Let's just go settle the score with him.
[Invitation]
Please, My Lords.
You truly are Divine Constables of the Divine Constable Bureau.
You've only been in Mingling for a few days,
and you've already eliminated the green-haired demon
and caught
Zhe Shan's murderer.
I am truly impressed.
I have specially prepared some wine and dishes
to celebrate your success and welcome you, My Lords.
Come, My Lords, please have a seat.
Lord Yan,
what is the meaning of this?
According to our dynasty's etiquette,
royalty who break the law do not wear cangues.
Since you are
Princess Ding's cousin,
whether you wear these shackles or not
is up to you.
But for the crimes you have committed,
we will definitely pursue them to the end.
So you are all here
to condemn me.
Then I would like to ask you, My Lords.
What crime have I committed?
Twelve years ago on Mount Fuyao,
you had your dogs attack
and kill someone, and buried the body.
So Xia Jiuying
still managed to piece her mother together.
This fool.
My Lords,
you don't think
you can convict me with just
a bunch of rotten bones, do you?
Your butler, Huang Bingshui,
is currently at the county office,
having a heart-to-heart talk with Lord Situ.
Why not
invite them to the Tingchao Boat
and talk while we eat?
Huang Bingshui...
Huang Bingshui
is an ungrateful traitor.
You actually believe what he says?
Back then,
if he hadn't failed to hold on
to that dog...
Now he's turning around and accusing me.
I think
he's worse than a dog!
My Lords.
Wasn't she just a village woman?
Is it worth making you all
go to such great lengths
and ruin your mood?
Why don't we
sit down and drink?
You have no regard for the law whatsoever,
do you?
Lord Yan.
We are here to investigate a case.
Since we are here to investigate,
we must follow the rules.
However,
what Mr. Ji just said
is indeed true.
Even a saint
couldn't tolerate this.
Is that so?
-Li Si, you... -This slap
is to vent some anger on behalf
of Xia Jiuying and her mother.
You...
This slap
is on behalf of the people
of Mingling County,
for your cruelty and for running a Hound Pit.
Lord Li.
Calm down.
Didn't you just say
that we must follow the rules when handling cases?
Mr. Ji.
Ms. Bai is right.
Just now,
I lost my temper.
Please forgive me.
Men!
Mr. Ji.
Capture them all!
I don't care what bureau you're from.
No authority can help you here.
Today,
none of you will leave here alive!
What do you want?
Where do you think you're going?
Stay away!
Stay away! Stay away!
-Stay away! -Stop!
Stay away!
The Divine Constable Bureau is killing people!
The Divine Constable Bureau is killing...
[Ji Mansion]
Second Master!
Bad news! Bad news!
B-Bad news.
Something terrible has happened.
Why are you panicking?
Master, he...
Master fell into the sea!
Has he been rescued?
N-No.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and find him.
Yes, yes.
Two of you, move this away.
Okay.
Come, put it here.
This side needs to be cleaned up too.
Okay.
Come, put it here.
Your martial arts have improved.
The rock crumbled like
a block of salt in your hand.
This is a block of salt.
It really is.
Huang Bingshui was right.
The Hound Pit appeared to be an underground fighting ring,
but it's actually a warehouse for hiding government salt.
So
this government salt
was usually right under our feet.
But making so much salt
must have required
a massive salt pan.
Did no one find out?
This salt
may not have been made by the Ji family themselves.
Don't forget
what the Gong family
of Mingling County does.
Transporting government salt.
They're embezzling imperial property.
What Gong Le told us that day
about the Gong family selling government salt
seems to be true now.
But aren't the Gong family and the Ji family
sworn enemies?
How could they collude?
My Lords.
Have you found Ji Ada?
Not yet.
These past few days, our men
have searched all the nearby beaches
and haven't found Ji Ada's body.
Lord Situ asked me to come and ask
if we should keep searching.